Guide to the Rice News photo files, 1995-2006 UA 357
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice News photo files
1995-2006
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 357
11 Linear Feet (22 boxes)
These records mostly include the photographs and negatives taken by Rice News photographers, as well as digital image files and copies of individual newspapers.
Biographical/Historical Note
The Rice News, published for Rice faculty and staff, began in the summer of 1991. It was produced on a weekly basis starting that fall, and continued until 2007. In April of 2007, Rice News ended its print version and transitioned into an online version to provide web-based, real-time information for its audience.
Scope and Contents Note
These records mostly include the photographs and negatives taken by Rice News photographers, as well as digital image files and copies of individual newspapers.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research. Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials were donated by Rice News. We also received digital images covering the issues from May 1996-July 1997. Because some or all of the images were low quality, were not owned by Rice, and/or corresponded to photographs and negatives in the physical files, we did not keep the digital images.
Accruals Note
Additional materials are expected for this collection.
Index Terms
Subjects
Newspapers; Universities and colleges
Document Types
photographs
- Series I: 1995-1999, 206899
  - Subseries A: 1995, 206900
    - July 27, 1995, 206901 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Photographs and negatives include: William Broyles, Anita K. Jones, James R. Pomerantz, Mike Meyers, Caroline Garcia, Mary Brown, Paul Harcombe, and Elgene Box.
    - August 24, 1995, 206903 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Beth Shapiro, Maryana Iskander, Christy Hard, Lisa Jones, Sheikh Hussein A. Al-Banawi, Malcolm Gillis, Lia Unrau, and Lisa Nutting.
    - August 31, 1995, 206904 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Willy Zwaenepoel, Ken Hatfield, Rape Aggression Defense Systems, Grand Organ in the Edyth Bates Old Recital Hall, Rice Owls football team, O-Week, and the Marching Owl Band.
    - September 7, 1995, 206905 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Photographs, negatives, and slides include: Roger Penrose, Michael Novak, Nancy Boothe, Steve Sutton, Jason Hafner, Andreas Thess, Nanotechnology, and Shannon Brown.
    - September 14, 1995, 206906 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: Mary Voswinkel, David Newman, Stephen Acker, Ray Scholton, David Sedmak, Alvin Jones, Tina McDuell, John Sprague, Deborah Washington, Les Hulsey, Jim Baylor, Steve Cox, Randy Hulet, Aileen Langston, Malcolm Gillis, Don Turley, Bobby May, Felicia Cavallini, and Olivier Olivier by Agnieszka Holland.
    - September 21, 1995, 206907 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Chandler Davidson, Sally Shelton, Norman Hackerman, Malcolm Gillis, Phillip A. Griffiths, Katherine E. Collins, Sgt. Willie Anderson, and the "Seductive Matter" exhibit at Rice University Gallery.
    - September 28, 1995, 206908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Roger Penrose, Paul Engle, Meg Grulee, B.B. King, Michael Hunt, Zenaido Camacho, Joan Strassman, Malcolm Gillis, and Dan Morales.
    - October 5, 1995, 206909 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Families' Weekend, "Citta Aperta-Open City" exhibit by Luciano Rigolini in Farish Gallery, Harold Hyman, Gale Stokes, Albert Van Helden, Bob Stein, Pierre Stoot and the Zydeco Dots, and the Shepherd School Marimba Quartet.
    - October 12, 1995, 206910 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Monica Martinez, Computational Engineering building construction, George Hirasaki, Robert Szafranski, Douglas Lindblad, John Clark, Scottie McDonald, Irie Time, David Queller, Elisabeth Arevalo, Joan Strassman, Joe Davidson, Carlos Garcia, Rice Club Cricket team, Darra Keeton, Malcolm Gillis, and Toshiyuki Kono.
    - October 19, 1995, 206911 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Kuiper Airborne Observatory event at the Museum of Natural Science, Y. David Chung's "Turtle Boat Head," Dale Sawyer, NASA images, and Department of Geology and Geophysics images.
    - October 26, 1995, 206912 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Steve Sutton, Brian Huberman, James A. Baker III, Linda Cooper, Mona Hicks, Catherine McKay, Minerva Garcia, Norberto Codina Boeras, Rice Memorial Center golden trophy cabinet, Student Center lounge, The Oil Makers by Jeffrey Share, and Mindy Vanderford.
    - November 2, 1995, 206913 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bowen Loftin, Homi Bhabha, Elizabeth Burr, James Carson, Hannu Miettinen, Bruce Knuteson, Emily Meyer, Peter Rogers, Janet Martin, Lin Yue, Malcolm Gillis, Paul Albright, Susan Bischoff, Cynthia Allshouse, and Dianne Bynum.
    - November 9, 1995, 206914 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Steve Sutton and Renae Scott.
    - November 16, 1995, 206915 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Roberto Rossellini's "Voyage to Italy."
    - November 17, 1995, 206916 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives of the Baker Conference Commemorative Issue include: Malcolm Gillis, George H.W. Bush, James A. Baker III, and Colin Powell.
    - November 30, 1995, 206917 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Photographs include: Jon Decoteau and Michael Carroll.
    - December 7, 1995, 206918 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice Owls football, Rice Homecoming, Erich Lethmeyer, Ken Whitmire, King Hill, Dicky Maegle, Rice Owls cheerleaders, Rice architecture students in at the house of Carlos Raul Villanueva, Nafis Sadik, Malcolm Gillis, Zenaido Camacho, Houston-area Hispanic Business magazine's top 500 list luncheon, and the "Explosion of Chemistry" Owlchemy show.
    - December 14, 1995, 206919 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Photographs and negatives include: Shengyun Qiu, Malcolum Gillis, Martha Wong, and Greg Yerington.
  - Subseries B: 1996, 206902
    - January 11, 1996, 206920 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Photographs and negatives include: Lucy Hernandez, John Gomez, Sarah Marsh, Sujata Mody, Patricia Martin, Allison Dubinsky, Jennifer Tucker, Gary Denmon, Computational Engineering building construction, Glenn C. Loury, Rice University basketball, Malcolm Gillis, and the Black Student Association vigil for Martin Luther King, Jr.
    - January 18, 1996, 206921 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Photographs and negatives include: J. Fred Duckett, Baudine Duckett, and the drill ship JOIDES Resolution.
    - January 25, 1996, 206922 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Photographs and negatives include: "An Caoin Ardaigh" Rice University Art Gallery installation by Michael Shaughnessy, Glenn C. Loury, Lee P. Brown, Samitra Seals, Maryana Iskander, Dean Currie, Tara Long, and the Black Student Association vigil for Martin Luther King Jr.
    - February 1, 1996, 206923 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Photographs and negatives include: Susan McIntosh, Roderick McIntosh, the Rice Archaeology Laboratory, Pol D. Spanos, Julia Amborski, the Go Texan Committee annual chili cookoff, Roger Labojasky, Mo Labojasky, Steve Matthews, Allen Ovum, Gary Cameron, Catherine Keneally, Marion Hicks, and Cornelius James.
    - February 8, 1996, 206924 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Photographs and negatives include: Vanessa Redgraves, Jon Weisheit, Rice Women "Celebrations, Challenges, Possibilities" Conference, Pol Spanos, Louis Malle, and Edward Djerejian.
    - February 15, 1996, 206925 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bren Dubay, Peter K. Karapetkov, Rice Women's Conference, Rice Women's Resource Center, Jennifer Olson, Chelsea Valdes, Barbara Jordan Tribute, Kirbyjon Caldwell, Stephen Klineberg, Chandler Davidson, Walter Hall, the Reverend Bill Lawson, Malcolm Gillis, Sheila Jackson Lee, and Lee Brown.
    - February 22, 1996, 206926 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Devika Subramanian, construction of Grand Organ for the Edyth Bates Old Recital Hall, Rice students playing Frisbee, David Applegate, and William Cook.
    - February 29, 1996, 206927 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Billy Bonner and Janet Braam.
    - March 14, 1996, 206928 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Judith Kelleher Schafer, Names Project AIDS Memorial Quilt, "Mountain Folks of Yunnan" Rice Media Center exhibit by Wu Jialin, Stephen Klineberg, and the Spring Theatre Festival.
    - March 21, 1996, 206929 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: William Marsh Rice, Willy's 180th Birthday Celebration, chorus dancers in "The Tender Land" opera, Katherine Drew, Clarence Martin, Raymond Martin, Computational Engineering or Duncan Hall building construction.
    - March 28, 1996, 206930 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Joel Cyprus, Jerry R. Junkins, Thomas J. Engibous, Malcolm Gillis, Sidney Burrus, Michael Carroll, and Isaac Christopher (Ike) Sanders.
    - April 4, 1996, 206931 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Chris Gouge, Todd Stadler, Patricia Bellan-Gillen, Ryan Levy, Scott Ruthfield, Beer Bike, and Brown College Women's Bike Team.
    - April 11, 1996, 206932 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: E. William "Bill" Barnett, Christine McPeters, "Angleton Grill" by Bren Dubay, John Freeman, Catherine Clack, Rice United for Diversity rally, Maryana Iskander, Malcolm Gillis, Dennis Huston, Soumtra Lahiri, Rice: The Next Century Stragic Plan, and John Strickland.
    - April 18, 1996, 206933 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: The Gardner Symonds Teaching Laboratory, "Breakthrough: The Changing Face of Science in America," Malcolm Gilis, William "Bill" Barnett, 33rd Annual Student Art Exhibition, Richard Tapia, Kathy Ireland, Whitfield Lovell, Paul Cooper, and student artwork by C. Miller, Hite Billes, Jesse DeMartino, and Timothy Carroll.
    - April 25, 1996, 206934 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Richard Brown, Hugh Hunt, James Young, Michael Hammond, Maryana Iskander, Anthony Elam, Seiichi Matsuda, Qimiao Si, Bruce Lairson, Katherine Fischer Drew Endowment, Janelle Scott, RiceFest, Dell Butcher Hall maps, and Emily Velz.
    - May 2, 1996, 206935 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Andrew Barron, Zenaido Camacho, Consular Ladies Club of Houston, Xie Jue, Mariella Salvatori, Patricia Martin, and Rice Engineering Alumni 1996 Annual Student Awards Ceremony and Barbecue.
    - May 9, 1996, 206936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Alex Ferrance, Commencement stage construction, Maria Teresa Leal, Eric Sutton, Thomas Estle, Oscar Byrd, Katherine Drew, Michael Maas, Deborah Harter, Ed Cox, John Hutchinson, and John Ambler.
    - May 30, 1996, 206937 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Commencement, Jesse DeMartino, Karin Broker, Malcolm Gillis, Tony Gorry, Taft Symonds, and French Pi Delta Phi Honors reception.
    - June 27, 1996, 206938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Photographs include: Texas World Police Games, Sgt. Willie Anderson, Robert Redman, Ed Ahnert, Malcolm Gillis, Terry Koonce, Albert Kidd, Kathy Balshaw-Biddle, Jonathan Miller, Pam Reynolds, Faculty Council Report on Salaries, Rice Baseball Camp, Paul Anderson, Dennis Hendrix, Christopher James Castaneda, David Auston, and Nancy Boothe.
    - July 25, 1996, 206939 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Photographs include: Harry K. Smith, Patrick Hartigan, Reginald Dufour, David Kaplan, Ron Sass, Linda McNeil, Kathryn Costello, Judith Brown, Joe Nelson, Macondo Brown-O'Connor, Nancy Boothe, Paul Anderson, David Auston, Dennis Hendrix, Robert Hunsacker, Christopher Castaneda, Tommy LaVergne, Kathryn Costello, Pat Kambhu, Jeff Cox, Devika Subramanian, Stephanie Weirich, Rice Web Camp, Kathy Mathison, trees, and Adam Setliff.
    - August 22, 1996, 206940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Hugh O'Brian, Hugh O'Brian Youth Foundation, Malcolm Gillis, Lou Aronica, Rice University Publishing Program, William W. Symes, Richard Tapia, Stewart A. Levin, and the Museum of Fine Arts exhibit of Frank Freed.
    - August 29, 1996, 206941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Malcolm Gillis, John Zammito, Ian Walker, John Hutchinson, Lori Rudge, Zenaido Camacho, Janet McNeill, Scott Biddy, Hanadi Ritai, Maryana Iskander, Leonel J. Castillo, Jenn Healey, and Rice matriculation.
    - September 5, 1996, 206942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ken Masters, Amy Calcote, Katy Densmore, Erin Devitt, Alex Hernandez, Clarence Miller, and Rice Orientation Week (O-Week).
    - September 12, 1996, 206943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Gary Soto, Anne Papakonstantinou, Russ Senti, Cynthia Larius, Edward McDonald, Sidney Burrus, Larry Tomkin, Keith Baggerly, the Western Athletic Conference, Richard Tapia, Dr. Austin, Ira Gruber, Patricia Gruber, Atieno Odhiambo, A. Miele, Marco Ciufolini, and Alan Dershowitz.
    - September 19, 1996, 206944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: William "Bill" Martin, Marching Owl Band uniform, Angela Valenzuela, Emilio Zamora, Clara Valenzuela-Zamora, Luz Valenzuela-Zamora, John Gladu, Jonna Beck, Allison Zumbro, Madeline Gladu, Ryan McMullan, Jennifer Ngo, Andy Hickl, and Eric Weimer.
    - September 26, 1996, 206945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Diana Welch, John Cirilo, Christof Spieler, William McNally, Elizabeth George, Jack Cadden, Stephanie Fuller, Catherine Clack, Patricia Bass, Mark Scheid, Patricia Martin, Lindley Doran, Times Barber Shop, Barber's Day, John Hutchinson, Dennis Huston, Sidney Burrus, Robert Stein, Carol Quillen, Kathleen Matthews, Arthur Gottschalk, Samuel Jones, and Ellsworth Milburn.
    - October 3, 1996, 206946 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Mark Ditman, Adeela Gill, John Campbell, Kari Hoffman, Elizabeth Oehler, Natalie Kirilcuk, Elizabeth Davis, Kelley Lounge, Rice Memorial Center, Veda Murthy, Jeff Barroso, Kieren MacMillan, Roberta Prior, Sasha Callahan, Emily Mann, Sammy's, and Amy Gutmann.
    - October 10, 1996, 206947 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Robert Curl, Nobel Prize, Fred Tomaselli "The Urge to be Transported" exhibit at the Rice University Art Gallery, Allison Fine, Malcolm Gillis, and Christopher Browning.
    - October 17, 1996, 206948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: Alan Thornhill, George Golka, Tomasz Golka, Rice Women's Fast-Pitch Team, Catherine McIntosh, Ann Zumwalt, Aimee Marchand, and Rice Homecoming.
    - October 24, 1996, 206949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Zenaido Comacho, Alex Hernandez, Chris Adolph, Anne Klein, Sarah Klizas, Tibetan lama Khetsun Sangpo Rinpoche, Malcolm Gillis, Marvin Zindler, Linda Neagley, Gothic architecture, Jack Rakove, and Steve Moniaci.
    - October 31, 1996, 206950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Connie Burke, John Outram, Francis L. Loewenheim, Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall), Hanan Ashrawi, and Werner Herzog.
    - November 7, 1996, 206951 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Amir NAderi, "New York City Walls 1990s" at the Rice University Media Center, Jennifer K. Holmes, Frances H. Jeter, J. Joseph Barnes, Fedwa Malti-Douglas, Sharon Durbin, Captain W. O. "Woe" King, President George H. W. Bush, President Gerald Ford, Malcolm Gillis, Lee Brown, U.N. Secretary General Boutros Gali, Baker Institute for Public Policy, Edward Djerejian, Jim Dunlap, Rice Homecoming, Ann Duncan, Charles Duncan, and the Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall).
    - November 15, 1996, 206952 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives in the Baker Conference Special Edition include: Jane Chance, Tolkien class, Rice Intramural College Bowl (Quiz Bowl), Daphne Gallagher, Rod Ganske, Andy Monat, Jay Welch, Janet Reno, Outer Loop construction, Lee Brown, Edward Djerejian, George R. Zodrow, Robert Stein, James A. Baker III, and Jack Kemp.
    - November 21, 1996, 206953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Eve Andree Laramee, Tom Williams, Dean Currie, David Bixler, Barry Dunning, Marjorie Corcoran, and Philip Mallory Jones.
    - December 5, 1996, 206955 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Ayisha McMillan, Saul Landau, Brian Huberman, John Hutchinson, Paula Hutchinson, John Boles, Bob Bixby, Betty Bixby, Ina C. Smith, Ron Sass, Bill Gordon, Cal Smith, J. Fred Duckett, Alan Grob, Kim Henkel, Al Gore, Richard Smalley, Robert Curl, and Douglas Osheroff.
    - December 12, 1996, 206956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: Chris Sankey, Carmen Flores, Anita Camargo, Jennifer Overton, Sharon Bush, Renae Scott, Keith Chapman, Heather Dodge, Carolynn White, Rita Loucks, Nora Quiocho, Phoebe Ruehl, Bud Smith, and the Best Buddies Rice chapter.
    - Spring 1996, 206965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Photographs and negatives include: 'Wild Art' and quad construction.
    - Summer 1996, 206975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: 'Wild Art,' construction, and Rice baseball camp.
  - Subseries C: 1997, 206957
    - January 16, 1997, 206958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Photographs and negatives include: George Marcus, Abdel Hernandez, Surpik Angelini, Nancy Burch, Richard Avant, Malcolm Gillis, Benjamin Bailar, Noah Reiter, Christine Young, Barbara Phelps, and Rice Emergency Medical Services.
    - January 23, 1997, 206959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: ice storm, Patrick Chang, Sungho Hwang, Scott Follmar, Anthony Postert, Neil Arnwine, John Schroeter, Thomas Nichols, and Valhalla.
    - January 30, 1997, 206960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Bill Lawson, Amy Chan, BSA Gospel Chorale, Zenaido Camacho, Black Student Association Candlelight Vigil, Jessica Cohen, Richard Smith, Asian Studies, Eric Brown, Malcolm Gillis, and Andre Droxler.
    - February 6, 1997, 206961 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Photographs and negatives include: Joseph Cathey, Michael Carroll, Sol LeWitt Rice University Art Gallery exhibit, and the Rice Model Science Laboratory Project.
    - February 13, 1997, 206962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Photographs and negatives include: John Cheatham, Malcolm Gillis, Stephanie Fuller, Alan Grob, Katherine Drew, Harold Hyman, Service Awards, Mary Margaret Williamson, Dominique DeMenil, James A. Baker III, Edward Djerejian, Madeleine Albright, Betty Charles, Eusebio Franco Jr., Bill Martin, and Marion Hicks.
    - February 20, 1997, 206963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Photographs and negatives include: Vivek Goel, Vivek Rao, Kim Manney Jones, Simi Blair, Vivek Pai, Vivek Ramarathnam, the Names Project AIDS Memorial Quilt, Cornel West, Malcolm Gillis, and Spring Outreach Day.
    - February 27, 1997, 206964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Photographs and negatives include: Allison Zumbro, Ryan McMullan, Samuel Jones, Tara Long, Stephanie Taylor, Mary Lou Margrave, Brooke Robertson, Michelle Washburn, Michelle O'Hara, Kathy Noack, Lindley Doran, Krista Ruth Noack, Laura Mize, Jasmin Tiro, Tara Long, Rachel Dornhelm, and Allison Fine.
    - March 13, 1997, 206966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Photographs and negatives include: Yasir Arafat, Larry Thompson, Samuel Jones, Malcolm Gillis, Edward Djerejian, and James A. Baker, III.
    - March 20, 1997, 206967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Photographs and negatives include: Eugen Radulescu, Beer Bike, Brown College Women's Team, Jones College students, Phil Gramm, Malcolm Gillis, Ann Greene, Michael Kinsley, and the 'Firing Line' debate.
    - March 27, 1997, 206968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Photographs and negatives include: Katharine Graham, Edward Djerejian, Anne Papakonstantinou, Fred Rudolph, and Nanda Kirkpatrick.
    - April 3, 1997, 206969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Photographs and negatives include: Willy's 181st Birthday, Josh Earnest, Brenna Copeland, Zenaido Comacho, Grand Organ in the Edyth Bates Old Recital Hall, Feliz Balderaz, Clyde Holloway, Margaret Fox, Malcolm Gillis, Melissa Straker, Victor Lopez, Andrea Blackett, TaNisha Mills, Robert Curl, and the Rice Men's Basketball team.
    - April 10, 1997, 206970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice Habitat for Humanity, Kevin Murphy, Mandy Hyland, Lillian Woung, Jonathan Cherry, Kim Ross, Frank Thorn, the Rice-Andersen House, Malcolm Gillis, Michael Hammond, Mary Lynn Marks, William "Bill" Barnett, Edyth Bates Old Recital Hall and Grand Organ dedication, and Virginia Babikian.
    - April 17, 1997, 206971 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Photographs and negatives include: Franz Brotzen, Sergio de los Cobos, Anne Walters Robinson, Edward Snow, Rice Men's Rugby Club, Vanessa Curto, David Minter, Caroline Minter, Calvin Class, Frances Brotzen, David Malone, Elizabeth Cook-Shen, Lucia Lin, Carl Feldbaum, George Mitchell, and Malcolm Gillis.
    - April 24, 1997, 206972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Photographs and negatives include: Brian Knowles, Sharon Bush, Rice University Student Art Exhibition No. 34, John Sparagana, Catherine Jones, Amanda Fisher, Jenne Giles, Gene Johnston, Rice Women's Lacrosse Club, Malcolm Gillis, Dan West, the Rice Forensics Society, the Baker Institute for Public Policy grand opening, and James A. Baker III.
    - May 8, 1997, 206973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Photographs and negatives include: George Burt, John Zammito, Emily Cheng, John Hutchinson, Marcin Szajda, Eugenia Georges, Stephen Klineberg, John Ambler, Chander Davidson, Elizabeth Long, Krista Noack, Kathy Noack, Joan Strassman, and Elysabeth Gamard.
    - May 29, 1997, 206974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Photographs, negatives, and slides include: Adam Reiser, Sylvia Morin, and the Pi Delta Phi French Honors Society.
    - June 26, 1997, 206976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photographs and negatives include: Matt Anderson, Lance Berkman, Wayne Graham, Jason Richards, Rice Owls Baseball, Doug Schuler, Ron Smith, Tracey Barbwell, Jack Redwine, Shirley Redwine, the iguana rescue, Darren Stockton, Larry Thompson, Roy Horner, Gabriel Orosco, and Fondren library construction.
    - July 31, 1997, 206977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Photographs, slides, and negatives include: Kevin Graham, Martin Pham, Robert Haymes, Christina Bui, Tim Wallace, Jamil Prentice, Ryan Dohoney, the Palmer Way Station, Urban Immersion Program, Helena Michie, Shirley Simpson, Rice-Andersen House, Yildiz Bayazitogiu, Theresa Chatman, Malcolm Gillis, Ken Kurtzman, John Hutchinson, John Dalton, and Richard Smalley.
    - August 28, 1997, 206978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Photographs and negatives include: Rice football, Rice Youth Football Day, Roger Hinshaw, Ken Hatfield, Malcolm Gillis, Robyn Wright Dunbar, Andrea Keys, Sheikh Hussein A. Al-Banawi, Mahmoud A. El-Gamal, Julie Francis, Rice cheerleaders, and Sean Williams.
    - September 4, 1997, 206979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Photographs and negatives include: Karin Broker, O-Week, '17 Years of Print Making' exhibit, Constance Estep Wells, Brian Knowles, Joseph Bartozek, Rice Sailing Club, Lucy Malone, Kent Voss, Malcolm Gillis, Team Wiess cheer, Daryl Shorter, Jones College, JIBA, Baker College car, matriculation, Baker 13, and Maria-Regina Kecht.